pearanalytics.com 2011-06-05

# Free SEO Analysis - Pear Analytics Website Analyzer

At Pear Analytics, we are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our visitors, and this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. At no time will we provide your personal information to any third party for the purpose of direct marketing. Information We Collect

We will collect and possibly store the following types of personal data as it pertains to you and your website:

1\. Information about your visits to the Pear Analytics retail website or application website(s);  
2\. Information about any transactions between you and Pear Analytics in relation to our web-based products;  
3\. Information that you provide to use for the purpose of registering for our products and/or other subscriptions/email/mobile phone notifications on our website or applications;

## Information About Your Website Visit

### Retail Website

We may collect information about your computer from the visit such as your IP address, geographic location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. We may use this information to improve the website’s usability and your overall experience. SiteJuice™ Product Application

We may collect information about your session such as feature usage, any and all data pertaining to the websites entered for analysis in your account, length of session, bandwidth usage, storage and other session related activities. External Web-Based Widgets

Pear Analytics offers the ability to use our Website Analyzer application externally by placing a script on any webpage. This application will ask for an email to retrieve a full, detailed report. These emails are never given to the host site for any reason, and are always controlled by Pear Analytics. Domain Verification

At this time we are not requiring ownership verification for domains entered into our SiteJuice™ application . All information and data collected from the domains entered into our tool are publicly accessible, such as source code, inbound link information, and other retrievable content that is publicly accessible and is able to be crawled by a search engine. This means that anyone at any time can analyze any website. If you do not want your website analyzed or crawled by our application, please notify us at support@pearanalytics.com. Using Your Personal Data

Personal data submitted on Pear Analytics’ retail website or SiteJuice™ application may be used in the following manners:

1\. To improve your browsing experience;  
2\. To contact you about feature updates and other special offers from Pear Analytics;  
3\. To contact you when scheduled reports are complete and ready for review;  
4\. Other types of communications related to your account.

### Disclosures

Situations may arise where we would have to disclose information about you:

1\. If we are required to do so by law;   
2\. In connection with any legal proceedings;  
3\. For the purposes of preventing fraud or reducing credit risk;

### Security of Your Personal Data

Pear Analytics takes all reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of your personal information. We never store or retrieve any credit card information for any reason. A secure merchant provider such as PayPal or Authorize.net handles all payment transactions. If you create an account, we do not have access to your password. If you lose your password, there is a password reset option on the login page.

### Policy Amendments

Pear Analytics reserves the right to update this privacy policy by posting a new version to our website.

### Cookies

Our retail website and SiteJuice™ application uses cookies for the purposes of remembering who you are when you return to the site.

### Contact

If you have any questions or concersns about this Privacy Policy on our treatment of your personal data, please email support@pearanalytics.com, or write to us at:

Pear Analytics  
Attn: Legal Department  
85 NE Loop 410  
Suite 570  
San Antonio, TX 78216
